

SOUN SAVDAN

Flutter Developer

About Me

Development using Flutter framework and Dart programming language Experience with mobile app development for iOS and Android platforms.

Successful release 4 apps to Google Play Store and App Store

- +855 98 88 34 04
- official.savdan@gmail.com
- Dangkao, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

LANGUAGE

- Khmer (Native)
- English (Basic)

PROGRAMMING

- Dart (Medium)
- JavaScript / Nodejs (Basic)
- OOP
- Java (Basic)
- C / C++ (Basic)
- SQL (Basic)

EXPERIENCE

Develop Flutter app at Biz Solution Aug 2022 - Present

Passionate and skilled Flutter Developer almost 3 years of experience in designing, developing, and deploying cross-platform mobile applications using Flutter and Dart. Adept at leveraging the full capabilities of the Flutter framework to create high-performance, visually appealing, and user-friendly mobile applications.

Flutter Developer internship at Inklusivity Aug 2021 - Nov 2021

Learning about Flutter app lifecycle maintenance and update exiting project using API HTTPS request and get JSON response.

Develop WordPress Site At CamConscious Tourism Nov 2019 - June 2020

Control the design and layout of a website using WordPress

theme and manage content on WordPress Site.

EDUCATION

Sok An Tonlap Hight School

Completed Bacc II 2015-2018

Royal University of Phnom Penh

Completed Bachelor degree 2018-2022

SKILLS SUMMARY

Flutter 70%

Research 75%

Strapi (CMS) - 20%

REFERENCE

Mos San

Business Acceleration Expert at Mission Alliance

Mobile : +855 17 39 48 80 Email : mos@nmakh.org

Suon Mach

Program officer and Social Worker at Family Fund for Children

Mobile: +855 96 63 22 653 Email: suonmach@ccf.org.tw